{"Questions": { "Question #60 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following describes the relationships among AWS Regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. There are more AWS Regions than Availability Zones.", "CORRECT:B. There are more edge locations than AWS Regions.", "C. An edge location is an Availability Zone.", "D. There are more AWS Regions than edge locations.", "CORRECT:E. There are more Availability Zones than AWS Regions."],"explanation": "","discussions": "2"}, "Question #61 Topic 2":{ "question":"What does AWS Shield Standard provide?", "answers":[ "A. WAF rules", "CORRECT:B. DDoS protection", "C. Identity and Access Management (IAM) permissions and access to resources", "D. Data encryption"],"explanation": "AWS Shield Standard provides protection for all AWS customers from common, most frequently occurring network and transport layer DDoS attacks that target your web site or application at no additional charge. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/shield/pricing/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #62 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to build its new application workloads in the AWS Cloud instead of using on-premises resources. What expense can be reduced using the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. The cost of writing custom-built Java or Node .js code", "B. Penetration testing for security", "CORRECT:C. hardware required to support new applications", "D. Writing specific test cases for third-party applications."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/cost-optimization/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #63 Topic 2":{ "question":"What does AWS Marketplace allow users to do? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Sell unused Amazon EC2 Spot Instances.", "CORRECT:B. Sell solutions to other AWS users.", "CORRECT:C. Buy third-party software that runs on AWS.", "D. Purchase AWS security and compliance documents.", "E. Order AWS Snowball."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace","discussions": "3"}, "Question #64 Topic 2":{ "question":"What does it mean if a user deploys a hybrid cloud architecture on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. All resources run using on-premises infrastructure.", "B. Some resources run on-premises and some run in a colocation center.", "C. All resources run in the AWS Cloud.", "CORRECT:D. Some resources run on-premises and some run in the AWS Cloud."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #65 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service allows users to identify the changes made to a resource over time?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Inspector", "CORRECT:B. AWS Config", "C. AWS Service Catalog", "D. AWS IAM"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/config/latest/developerguide/view-manage-resource.html","discussions": "3"}, "Question #66 Topic 2":{ "question":"How can a company reduce its Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) using AWS?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. By minimizing large capital expenditures", "B. By having no responsibility for third-party license costs", "C. By having no operational expenditures", "D. By having AWS manage applications"],"explanation": "Explanation - AWS helps you reduce Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) by reducing the need to invest in large capital expenditures and providing a pay-as-you-go model that empowers you to invest in the capacity you need and use it only when the business requires it. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #67 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which activity is a customer responsibility in the AWS Cloud according to the AWS shared responsibility model?", "answers":[ "A. Ensuring network connectivity from AWS to the internet", "B. Patching and fixing flaws within the AWS Cloud infrastructure", "C. Ensuring the physical security of cloud data centers", "CORRECT:D. Ensuring Amazon EBS volumes are backed up"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/the-aws-shared-responsibility-model-and-gdpr/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #68 Topic 2":{ "question":"What are the advantages of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Fixed rate monthly cost", "CORRECT:B. No need to guess capacity requirements", "CORRECT:C. Increased speed to market", "D. Increased upfront capital expenditure", "E. Physical access to cloud data centers"],"explanation": "Reference: https://data-flair.training/blogs/aws-advantages/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #69 Topic 2":{ "question":"When comparing the total cost of ownership (TCO) of an on-premises infrastructure to a cloud architecture, what costs should be considered? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. The credit card processing fees for application transactions in the cloud.", "CORRECT:B. The cost of purchasing and installing server hardware in the on-premises data.", "CORRECT:C. The cost of administering the infrastructure, including operating system and software installations, patches, backups, and recovering from failures.", "D. The costs of third-party penetration testing.", "E. The advertising costs associated with an ongoing enterprise-wide campaign."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #70 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS feature allows a company to take advantage of usage tiers for services across multiple member accounts?", "answers":[ "A. Service control policies (SCPs)", "CORRECT:B. Consolidated billing", "C. All Upfront Reserved Instances", "D. AWS Cost Explorer"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #71 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is one of the customer's responsibilities according to the AWS shared responsibility model?", "answers":[ "A. Virtualization infrastructure", "B. Network infrastructure", "CORRECT:C. Application security", "D. Physical security of hardware"],"explanation": "Reference: https://cloudacademy.com/blog/aws-shared-responsibility-model-security/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #72 Topic 2":{ "question":"What helps a company provide a lower latency experience to its users globally?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Using an AWS Region that is central to all users", "B. Using a second Availability Zone in the AWS Region that is using used", "C. Enabling caching in the AWS Region that is being used", "D. Using edge locations to put content closer to all users"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/six-advantages-of-cloud-computing.html","discussions": "16"}, "Question #73 Topic 2":{ "question":"How can the AWS Cloud increase user workforce productivity after migration from an on-premises data center?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Users do not have to wait for infrastructure provisioning.", "B. The AWS Cloud infrastructure is much faster than an on-premises data center infrastructure.", "C. AWS takes over application configuration management on behalf of users.", "D. Users do not need to address security and compliance issues."],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Migration/aws-migration-whitepaper.pdf","discussions": "1"}, "Question #74 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides a quick and automated way to create and manage AWS accounts?", "answers":[ "A. AWS QuickSight", "B. Amazon Lightsail", "CORRECT:C. AWS Organizations", "D. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/mt/automate-account-creation-and-resource-provisioning-using-aws-service-catalog-aws-organizations-and-aws- lambda/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #75 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which Amazon RDS feature can be used to achieve high availability?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Multiple Availability Zones", "B. Amazon Reserved Instances", "C. Provisioned IOPS storage", "D. Enhanced monitoring"],"explanation": "Explanation - Amazon RDS provides high availability and failover support for DB instances using Multi-AZ deployments. Amazon RDS uses several different technologies to provide failover support. Multi-AZ deployments for Oracle, PostgreSQL, MySQL, and MariaDB DB instances use Amazon's failover technology. SQL Server DB instances use SQL Server Database Mirroring (DBM). Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/Concepts.MultiAZ.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #76 Topic 2":{ "question":"Where should users report that AWS resources are being used for malicious purposes?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Abuse team", "B. AWS Shield", "C. AWS Support", "D. AWS Developer Forums"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/report-aws-abuse/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #77 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service needs to be enabled to track all user account changes within the AWS Management Console?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS CloudTrail", "B. Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)", "C. VPC Flow Logs", "D. AWS CloudHSM"],"explanation": "Explanation - AWS CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational auditing, and risk auditing of your AWS account. With CloudTrail, you can log, continuously monitor, and retain account activity related to actions across your AWS infrastructure. CloudTrail provides event history of your AWS account activity, including actions taken through the AWS Management Console, AWS SDKs, command line tools, and other AWS services. This event history simplifies security analysis, resource change tracking, and troubleshooting. In addition, you can use CloudTrail to detect unusual activity in your AWS accounts. These capabilities help simplify operational analysis and troubleshooting. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #78 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is an AWS Cloud design best practice?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Tight coupling of components", "B. Single point of failure", "C. High availability", "D. Overprovisioning of resources"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","discussions": "18"}, "Question #79 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following is an example of how moving to the AWS Cloud reduces upfront cost?", "answers":[ "A. By replacing large variable costs with lower capital investments", "CORRECT:B. By replacing large capital investments with lower variable costs", "C. By allowing the provisioning of compute and storage at a fixed level to meet peak demand", "D. By replacing the repeated scaling of virtual servers with a simpler fixed-scale model"],"explanation": "AWS does not require minimum spend commitments or long-term contracts. You replace large upfront expenses with low variable payments that only apply to what you use. With AWS you are not bound to multi-year agreements or complicated licensing models. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/economics/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #80 Topic 2":{ "question":"When designing a typical three-tier web application, which AWS services and/or features improve availability and reduce the impact failures? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Auto Scaling for Amazon EC2 instances", "B. Amazon VPC subnet ACLs to check the health of a service", "CORRECT:C. Distributed resources across multiple Availability Zones", "D. AWS Server Migration Service (AWS SMS) to move Amazon EC2 instances into a different Region", "E. Distributed resources across multiple AWS points of presence"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","discussions": "4"}, "Question #81 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which cloud design principle aligns with AWS Cloud best practices?", "answers":[ "A. Create fixed dependencies among application components", "B. Aggregate services on a single instance", "C. Deploy applications in a single Availability Zone", "CORRECT:D. Distribute the compute load across multiple resources"],"explanation": "Use load balancing for offloading encryption termination (TLS) to improve performance and to manage and route traffic effectively. Distribute traffic across multiple resources or services to allow your workload to take advantage of the elasticity that AWS provides. Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/architecture/AWS_Well-Architected_Framework.pdf","discussions": "1"}, "Question #82 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are recommended practices for managing IAM users? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Require IAM users to change their passwords after a specified period of time", "CORRECT:B. Prevent IAM users from reusing previous passwords", "C. Recommend that the same password be used on AWS and other sites", "D. Require IAM users to store their passwords in raw text", "E. Disable multi-factor authentication (MFA) for IAM users"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #83 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company is migrating from on-premises data centers to the AWS Cloud and is looking for hands-on help with the project. How can the company get this support? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Ask for a quote from the AWS Marketplace team to perform a migration into the company's AWS account.", "CORRECT:B. Contact AWS Support and open a case for assistance", "CORRECT:C. Use AWS Professional Services to provide guidance and to set up an AWS Landing Zone in the company's AWS account", "D. Select a partner from the AWS Partner Network (APN) to assist with the migration", "E. Use Amazon Connect to create a new request for proposal (RFP) for expert assistance in migrating to the AWS Cloud."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/solutions/aws-landing-zone/","discussions": "12"}, "Question #84 Topic 2":{ "question":"How does the AWS Enterprise Support Concierge team help users?", "answers":[ "A. Supporting application development", "B. Providing architecture guidance", "CORRECT:C. Answering billing and account inquires", "D. Answering questions regarding technical support cases"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","discussions": "14"}, "Question #85 Topic 2":{ "question":"An application designed to span multiple Availability Zones is described as:", "answers":[ "A. being highly available", "B. having global reach", "C. using an economy of scale", "CORRECT:D. having elasticity"],"explanation": "Reference: https://books.google.com.pk/books?id=IueWBQAAQBAJ&pg=PA11&lpg=PA11&dq=aws+application+designed+to+span+multiple+Availability+Zones +is+described+as+economy+of+scale&source=bl&ots=cj_NsIAXm2&sig=ACfU3U2fe5KOugmORbAoV9lgj_eCGlsltA&hl=en&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiGzf- rtbroAhVkxoUKHRhjC-IQ6AEwCnoECAkQAQ#v=onepage&q=aws%20application%20designed%20to%20span%20multiple%20Availability%20Zones%20is% 20described%20as%20economy%20of%20scale&f=false","discussions": "11"}, "Question #86 Topic 2":{ "question":"A new service using AWS must be highly available. Yet, due to regulatory requirements, all of its Amazon EC2 instances must be located in a single geographic area. According to best practices, to meet these requirements, the EC2 instances must be placed in at least two:", "answers":[ "A. AWS Regions", "CORRECT:B. Availability Zones", "C. subnets", "D. placement groups"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/faqs/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #87 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS tool is used to compare the cost of running an application on-premises to running the application in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "CORRECT:C. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "D. Cost Explorer"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #88 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company has multiple AWS accounts within AWS Organizations and wants to apply the Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances benefit to a single account only. Which action should be taken?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Purchase the Reserved Instances from master payer account and turn off Reserved Instance sharing.", "B. Enable billing alerts in the AWS Billing and Cost Management console.", "C. Purchase the Reserved Instances in individual linked accounts and turn off Reserved Instance sharing from the payer level.", "D. Enable Reserved Instance sharing in the AWS Billing and Cost Management console."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/ec2-ri-consolidated-billing/","discussions": "12"}, "Question #89 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which situation should be reported to the AWS Abuse team?", "answers":[ "A. In Availability Zone has a service disruption", "CORRECT:B. An intrusion attempt is made from an AWS IP address", "C. A user has trouble accessing an Amazon S3 bucket from an AWS IP address", "D. A user needs to change payment methods due to a compromise"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/report-aws-abuse/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #90 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company is planning to launch an ecommerce site in a single AWS Region to a worldwide user base. Which AWS services will allow the company to reach users and provide low latency and high transfer speeds? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Application Load Balancer", "B. AWS Global Accelerator", "C. AWS Direct Connect", "CORRECT:D. Amazon CloudFront", "E. AWS Lambda"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/faqs/","discussions": "11"}, "Question #91 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service or resource is serverless?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Lambda", "B. Amazon EC2 instances", "C. Amazon Lightsail", "D. Amazon ElastiCache"],"explanation": "Reference: https://blogs.itemis.com/en/serverless-services-on-aws","discussions": "2"}, "Question #92 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are components of Amazon VPC? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Objects", "CORRECT:B. Subnets", "C. Buckets", "CORRECT:D. Internet gateways", "E. Access key"],"explanation": "Reference: https://subscription.packtpub.com/book/virtualization_and_cloud/9781788293723/3/ch03lvl1sec26/vpc-components","discussions": "1"}, "Question #93 Topic 2":{ "question":"AWS Budgets can be used to:", "answers":[ "A. prevent a given user from creating a resource", "B. send an alert when the utilization of Reserved Instances drops below a certain percentage", "CORRECT:C. set resource limits in AWS accounts to prevent overspending", "D. split an AWS bill across multiple forms of payment"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/budgets-managing-costs.html","discussions": "12"}, "Question #94 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following will enhance the security of access to the AWS Management Console? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Secrets Manager", "B. AWS Certificate Manager", "CORRECT:C. AWS Multi-Factor Authentication (AWS MFA)", "D. Security groups", "E. Password policies"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/guidelines-for-protecting-your-aws-account-while-using-programmatic-access/","discussions": "11"}, "Question #95 Topic 2":{ "question":"The AWS Trusted Advisor checks include recommendations regarding which of the following? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Information on Amazon S3 bucket permissions", "B. AWS service outages", "CORRECT:C. Multi-factor authentication enabled on the AWS account root user", "D. Available software patches", "E. Number of users in the account"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #96 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which functions can users perform using AWS KMS?", "answers":[ "A. Create and manage AWS access keys for the AWS account root user", "CORRECT:B. Create and manage AWS access keys for an AWS account IAM user", "C. Create and manage keys for encryption and decryption of data", "D. Create and manage keys for multi-factor authentication"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/kms/latest/developerguide/control-access.html","discussions": "9"}, "Question #97 Topic 2":{ "question":"How does AWS Trusted Advisor provide guidance to users of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. It identifies software vulnerabilities in applications running on AWS", "CORRECT:B. It provides a list of cost optimization recommendations based on current AWS usage", "C. It detects potential security vulnerabilities caused by permissions settings on account resources", "D. It automatically corrects potential security issues caused by permissions settings on account resources", "CORRECT:E. It provides proactive alerting whenever an Amazon EC2 instance has been compromised"],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #98 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are advantages of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS manages the maintenance of the cloud infrastructure", "B. AWS manages the security of applications built on AWS", "CORRECT:C. AWS manages capacity planning for physical servers", "D. AWS manages the development of applications on AWS", "E. AWS manages cost planning for virtual servers"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-center/controls/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #99 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user deploys an Amazon RDS DB instance in multiple Availability Zones. This strategy involves which pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Performance efficiency", "B. Reliability", "C. Cost optimization", "D. Security"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","discussions": "13"}, "Question #100 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services provide a user with connectivity between the AWS Cloud and on-premises resources? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS VPN", "B. Amazon Connect", "C. Amazon Cognito", "CORRECT:D. AWS Direct Connect", "E. AWS Managed Services"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/directconnect/ https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/networking-and-content-delivery/introducing-aws-client-vpn-to-securely-access-aws-and-on-premises-resources/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #101 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service is used to pay AWS bills, and monitor usage and budget costs?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Billing and Cost Management", "B. Consolidated billing", "C. Amazon CloudWatch", "D. Amazon QuickSight"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #102 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which element of the AWS global infrastructure consists of one or more discrete data centers, each with redundant power, networking, and connectivity, which are housed in separate facilities?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Regions", "CORRECT:B. Availability Zones", "C. Edge locations", "D. Amazon CloudFront"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/global-infrastructure.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #103 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which Amazon VPC feature enables users to capture information about the IP traffic that reaches Amazon EC2 instances?", "answers":[ "A. Security groups", "B. Elastic network interfaces", "C. Network ACLs", "CORRECT:D. VPC Flow Logs"],"explanation": "VPC Flow Logs is a feature that enables you to capture information about the IP traffic going to and from network interfaces in your VPC. Flow log data can be published to Amazon CloudWatch Logs or Amazon S3. After you've created a flow log, you can retrieve and view its data in the chosen destination. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/flow-logs.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #104 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service can be used to automatically scale an application up and down without making capacity planning decisions?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon AutoScaling", "B. Amazon Redshift", "C. AWS CloudTrail", "D. AWS Lambda"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/category/auto-scaling/","discussions": "11"}, "Question #105 Topic 2":{ "question":"AWS Enterprise Support users have access to which service or feature that is not available to users with other AWS Support plans?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS Support case", "CORRECT:C. Concierge team", "D. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #106 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to migrate a MySQL database to AWS but does not have the budget for Database Administrators to handle routine tasks including provisioning, patching, and performing backups. Which AWS service will support this use case?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon RDS", "B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon DocumentDB", "D. Amazon ElastiCache"],"explanation": "Amazon RDS makes it easy to set up, operate, and scale a relational database in the cloud. It provides cost-efficient and resizable capacity while automating time- consuming administration tasks, such as hardware provisioning, database setup, patching, and backups. It frees you to focus on your applications, so you can give them the fast performance, high availability, security, and compatibility that they need. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/database/part-1-role-of-the-dba-when-moving-to-amazon-rds-responsibilities/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #107 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to expand from one AWS Region into a second AWS Region. What does the company need to do to start supporting the new Region?", "answers":[ "A. Contact an AWS Account Manager to sign a new contract", "B. Move an Availability Zone to the new Region", "C. Begin deploying resources in the second Region", "CORRECT:D. Download the AWS Management Console for the new Region"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/emr/latest/ManagementGuide/emr-plan-region.html","discussions": "10"}, "Question #108 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user must meet compliance and software licensing requirements that state a workload must be hosted on a physical server. Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing option will meet these requirements?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Dedicated Hosts", "B. Dedicated Instances", "C. Spot Instances", "D. Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/dedicated-hosts/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #109 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service will provide a way to generate encryption keys that can be used to encrypt data? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Macie", "B. AWS Certificate Manager", "CORRECT:C. AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)", "D. AWS Secrets Manager", "CORRECT:E. AWS CloudHSM"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/crypto/latest/userguide/awscryp-service-hsm.html https://docs.aws.amazon.com/kms/latest/developerguide/overview.html","discussions": "2"}}}